const quizQuestions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Which method removes the last element from an array and returns that element?",
        choices: [
            "pop()",
            "shift()",
        ],
        answer: "pop()"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which method adds a new item to the end of an array?",
        choices: [
            "push()",
            "pop()"
        ],
        answer: "push()"
    },
/*    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which method creates a new array based on a selection?",
        choices: [
            "shift()",
            "appendChild()",
            "slice()",
            "push()"
        ],
        answer: "slice()"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which method adds a new item to the beginning of an array?",
        choices: [
            "unshift()",
            "pop()",
            "shift()",
            "slice()"
        ],
        answer: "unshift()"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which method removes the first element from an array and returns that element?",
        choices: [
            "push()",
            "slice()",
            "unshift()",
            "shift()"
        ],
        answer: "shift()"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which method rearranges the elements of an array into alphabetical or numerical order?",
        choices: [
            "every()",
            "reduce()",
            "sort()",
            "includes()"
        ],
        answer: "sort()"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Which method creates a new array, populated with the results of calling a provided function on every element in the calling array?",
        choices: [
            "map()",
            "filter()",
            "reduce()",
            "forEach()"
        ],
        answer: "map()"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Which method takes in an array, performs a function that you provide on each element in that array, and returns one single value?",
        choices: [
            "filter()",
            "forEach()",
            "map()",
            "reduce()"
        ],
        answer: "reduce()"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Which method performs a function that you provide on each element in that array, and returns only those elements that pass the test implemented by that function?",
        choices: [
            "every()",
            "filter()",
            "map()",
            "forEach()"
        ],
        answer: "filter()"
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Which method executes a provided function once for each element in an array?",
        choices: [
            "every()",
            "forEach()",
            "map()",
            "reduce()"
        ],
        answer: "forEach()"
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "Which method tests whether all elements in the array pass the test implemented by the provided function, returning a boolean (true/false) value?",
        choices: [
            "map()",
            "every()",
            "forEach()",
            "includes()"
        ],
        answer: "every()"
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "Which method determines whether an array contains a certain value among its entries, returning true or false as appropriate?",
        choices: [
            "every()",
            "includes()",
            "indexOf()",
            "pop()"
        ],
        answer: "includes()"
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: "Which method returns the first index at which a given element can be found in the array (or -1 if it is not present)?",
        choices: [
            "indexOf()",
            "includes()",
            "slice()",
            "map()"
        ],
        answer: "indexOf()"
    } */
];
